<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<testsuite failures="0" name="cucumber.runtime.formatter.JUnitFormatter" skipped="6" tests="6" time="0">
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="Adac" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[Given user Launch The Application...........................................undefined
When user Enter The "sivaprakashdivya" In Username Field....................undefined
And user Enter The "shivanya" In password Field.............................undefined
Then user Click On The Login Button And It Navigates To The Search Hotel Page.undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[When user Select The Location In Location Field.............................undefined
And user Select The Hotel In Hotel Field....................................undefined
And user Select The Room Type In RoomType Field.............................undefined
And user Select The No. Of Rooms In Room Field..............................undefined
And user Enters The Date In check In Date Field.............................undefined
And user Enters The Date In check Out Date Field............................undefined
And user Select Adults per Room In Adults per Room Field....................undefined
And user Select Children Per Room In Children per Room Field................undefined
Then user Click On The Search Button And It Navigates To The Select Hotel Page.undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[When user Click The Radio Button To Select The Hotel........................undefined
Then user Click On The Continue Button And It Navigates To The Booking Page.undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[When user Enter The Firstname In Firstname Field............................undefined
And user Enter The Lastname In Lastname Field...............................undefined
And user Enter The Address In Billing Address Field.........................undefined
And user Enter The Credit Card No. In Credit Card No. Field.................undefined
And user Select The Credit Card Type In Credit Card Type Field..............undefined
And user Select The Month In Expiry Date Field..............................undefined
And user Select The Year In Expiry Date Field...............................undefined
And user Enter The Cvv No. In Cvv Field.....................................undefined
Then user Click On The Book Now Button And It Navigates To The Booking Confirmation Page.undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[Then user Click On The My Itinerary Button And It Navigates To The Book Itinerary Page.undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
    <testcase classname="Hotel Booking In Adactin Application" name="" time="0">
        <skipped><![CDATA[Then user Click On The Logout Button And It Navigates To The Logout Page....undefined
]]></skipped>
    </testcase>
</testsuite>
